Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- Boise office, 4
  - Subject Files
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      INEL; Nuclear Waste; Yucca Mountain
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory: Clean Up, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      INEL; Nuclear Waste
      H.R.3894
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory: Craig Summit, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory: Federal Agreement, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory: Stop Waste Shipments, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Idaho National Guard, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Inheritance Taxation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Aged; Social Security; Long-Term Care Family Security Act
      H.R.4848
    - Intermodal Carrier Competitiveness, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Interstate Commerce; Freight Carriers
      H.R.3221
    - Israel, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - J. D. Williams, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Karcher Interchange-Nampa, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Canyon County--Roads
    - Kootenai County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Labor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Landfills, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Solid Waste; Environmental Protection Agency
    - Larry LaRocco, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Latah County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lottery, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Luxury Tax, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Taxation; Excise Tax
      H.R.2598
    - Mayor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Boise, Idaho
      Keiser, John H.
    - Mining, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Mountain Home Air Force Base, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Training Range
    - National Education Association, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - National Forests, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Naval Reactor Waste - INEL, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Nuclear Waste; Department of the Navy
    - Naval Reactor Waste - INEL, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Naval Reactor Waste - INEL, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Nez Perce County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Nuclear Energy, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      INEL; Nuclear Waste; Nuclear Weapons
    - Nuclear Power Reactor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      INEL; Nuclear Reactors
    - Nuclear Waste, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Nuclear Waste Negotiator: Leroy/Stallings, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      LeRoy, David; Stallings, Richard
    - Nuclear Waste: DOE Storage, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - One Percent Initiative, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      Campaign, 1992; Property Tax; Taxation
    - Owyhee County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Pacific Materials Exchange, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Payette County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Payette River, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      Hydroelectric Power
    - Payment in Lieu of Taxes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Taxation; Public Lands
    - President, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      Clinton, Bill; Bush, George; Perot, Ross
    - Railroad Union Strike, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Railroads--Strike; Freight Carriers
      Smeed, Ralph
    - Railroads, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Republican Party, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Rivers, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Idaho--Rivers; Drawdowns; Wild and Scenic Rivers
    - Salmon, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Salmon, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Idaho Law Review; University of Idaho
    - Salmon, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Salmon, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Salmon, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Salmon, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Salmon Working Group, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Savings and Loans, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Schweitzer Road, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Idaho--Roads; Schweitzer Mountain Road; Bonner County
    - Seniors, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Aged; Medical Care; Social Security
    - Shoshone County, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Bunker Hill Superfund; Silver Valley, Idaho
    - Silver, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Silver Mining; Silver Medal Act
    - Spent Nuclear Fuel Storage Facility, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Stallings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Stallings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Symms, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Taxes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Taxation; Government Spending
    - The "Vision" Thing, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Agriculture; Farming
    - Timber, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Timber, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Timber, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Timber, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Timber, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Timber Salvage Bill, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Timber Industry; Forest Salvage Bill; Forest Health Act
    - Town Meetings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Constituent Communication; Campaign, 1992
    - Town Meetings: Gulf Crisis, 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Constituent Communication; Persian Gulf War
    - Trade, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      NAFTA; GATT; International Economics
    - Trails, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      All Terrain Vehicles
    - Training Range, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Mountain Home Air Force Base; Owyhee County
    - Training Range, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Transit Funding, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Public Transportation
    - Transportation, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Transportation Systems; Roads--Safety
    - Transportation Reports, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Roads; Transportation Systems
    - Transportation/Training Amendment, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Nuclear Waste Transportation; INEL
      H.R.2356
    - Transportation/Training Amendment, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Nuclear Waste Transportation
      H.R.2637
    - Triumph Mine (Blaine County): Superfund, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
    - Valbois, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Valbois Resort; Valley County
    - Valley County, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      McCall, Idaho
    - Veterans, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Washington County, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Administration's Bill, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      New Mexico--Nuclear Waste
      H.R.1834
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Administrative Withdrawal #2, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Administrative Withdrawal #4, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Background, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Kostmayer's Bill - M.V., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Kostmayer, Peter
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Meeting - Move Log. w.d., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Skeen's Bill - Introduction, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Skeen, Joe; Stallings, Richard
    - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant: Visit by Larry LaRocco, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Water, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Water Resources; Drought
    - Weekly Columns, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Wilderness, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Wilderness Areas
    - Wildlife, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Hunting; Wildlife--Habitat
    - WIPP, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      INEL; Snake River Alliance; Nuclear Waste
    - Wolves, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Wolves--Environmental Aspects
    - Wolves, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Women, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Yellowstone Protection Act, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Yellowstone National Park; Water Resources; Old Faithful Protection Act
      H.R.1137
    - Yucca Mountain, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Yucca Mountain, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Issues
    - Balanced Budget, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Balanced Budget Amendment; Government Spending
    - Banking, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Banks and Banking; Fair Credit Reporting Act
    - Birds of Prey, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Snake River Birds of Prey Area; Bureau of Land Management
      Statement at Dedication of Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area 5/21/1994
    - Birds of Prey, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Snake River Birds of Prey Area; Bureau of Land Management; Grazing; Orchard Training Area; Idaho National Guard
    - Budget, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Budgets; Earned Income Tax Credit
    - Budget Reconciliation, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act
    - Campaign Materials, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Campaign, 1994; Rutherford Institute; Education; American Civil Liberties Union; Lobbyists
    - Campaign, 1992, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Campaign, 1992 Results, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Chenoweth Letter, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Choice, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Abortion; Freedom of Choice Act
    - Christian Right, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Campaign, 1994; Idaho Family Forum; Anti-Defamation League; Christian Coalition
    - Concord Goal, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Concord Coalition; Budget Deficits
      H.R.3355
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Constituent Communication; Campaign, 1994
    - Death Penalty, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Capital Punishment
    - Election, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Congressional Election, 1994; Campaign, 1994
    - Endangered Species Act Documents, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Bruneau Hot Springs Snail; Idaho Conservation League; Idaho Farm Bureau Federation
    - Fast Track, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      NAFTA; Treaties
    - Foreign Aid, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Policy, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Franking, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Grazing, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Public Lands; Bureau of Land Management
    - Health, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Health Security Act; Health Care Reform Plan
      H.R.3600
    - Health Care, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Hot File, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - House Post Office Scandal, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Housing, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - LaRocco for Congress, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Larry LaRocco: Bills, Etc., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Congress--Legislation
    - Legislature: Summaries, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Mountain Home Air Force Base, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Military Bases--Closure; Idaho Cattle Association
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Congress--Newsletters
    - Private Property, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Racial Justice Act, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Criminal Justice Act; Minorities; Omnibus Crime Bill
    - Regrets, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Salmon, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Scheduling Letters, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Appearances
    - Social Security, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Speeches, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Spending Cuts, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Term Limits, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Campaign Finance Reform
    - The "A to Z" Plan, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Veterans
    - Timber, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Timber Industry; Logging
    - Town Meetings, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Public Appearances
    - Training Range, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Mountain Home Air Force Base; Bighorn Sheep; Bombing Ranges
    - Training Range, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Bombing Ranges; Mountain Home Air Force Base; Owyhee County
    - Truth in Sentencing, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Crime; Legal System
    - U.S. Troops--Foreign Command, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Military
    - Veterans, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Veterans Affairs
    - Whitewater Investigation, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Whitewater, Arkansas
    - Wilderness, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      Wilderness Areas; Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Timber Industry
    - Wilderness, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Wilderness Areas; Idaho--Wilderness Areas
    - Wilderness, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Areas; Timber Industry Wilderness Areas--Economic Aspects; Public Lands
    - Wilderness, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Areas--Economic Aspects; Timber Industry
      Statement St. Maries Town Meeting 1/11/1993
    - Wilderness/Idaho, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Wilds, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Campaign
    - Ads, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Chenoweth, Helen; Church, Frank
    - Announcement, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Chenoweth - Chief of Staff, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Campaign, Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Choice, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Campaign, 1994; Abortion
    - Contract, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Campaign, 1994; Contract with America
    - Defamation Lawsuit, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Education, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Endangered Species/Salmon, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Campaign, 1994; Endangered Species Act
    - Endorsements, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Environment, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fund Raising/FEC, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Campaign, 1994; Campaign Financing
    - Gays, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Campaign, 1994; Homosexuality
    - General Election Results/Etc., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Healthcare, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Land Deal, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Campaign, 1994; Public Lands
    - Mining, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Campaign, 1994; Mines and Mining
    - Personal/Biography, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Polls, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Primary Campaign, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Religious/Extreme Right, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Campaign, 1994; Christian Coalition
    - Taxes, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Term Limits, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Timber, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Campaign, 1994; Timber Issue
    - Veterans, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - War on the West, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Water, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Campaign, 1994; Water Rights
    - Wilderness, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      Campaign, 1994; Wilderness Areas
    - Wise Use, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Campaign, 1994; Salmon
    - Press Releases, 1993 January (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Press Releases, 1993 February (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases, 1993 March (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Press Releases, 1993 April (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Press Releases, 1993 May (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Press Releases - June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Press Releases, 1993 July (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Press Releases, 1993 August (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Press Releases, 1993 September (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Press Releases, 1993 October (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Press Releases, 1993 November (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Press Releases, 1993 December (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Press Releases, 1994 January (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Press Releases, 1994 February (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Press Releases, 1994 March (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Press Releases, 1994 April (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Press Releases, 1994 May (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Press Releases, 1994 June (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Press Releases, 1994 July (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Press Releases, 1994 August (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Press Releases, 1994 September (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Press Releases, 1994 October, November (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Clippings
    - Abortion, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Academies, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Military Academies
    - Ada County, 1992,1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Adams County, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Wheat; Wool Act; Pesticides
    - Appointments, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Presidential Appointments
    - Banking (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Basque, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Basques
    - Benewah County, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Bio-Survey, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Natural Resources--Surveys; National Biological Survey
    - Birds of Prey, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      World Center for the Birds of Prey; Birds of Prey National Conservation Area
    - Boise County, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bonner County (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Boundary County, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of Land Management, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Business, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Cable Television, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - California Desert, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Wilderness; California Desert Protection Act
    - Canyon County, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Cattle: Grazing, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Cattle Industry; Public Lands
    - Chenoweth, Helen, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Children, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Family Services
    - Christian Right (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Political Action Groups; Christian Coalition
    - Civil Rights, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Clearwater County, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Dworshak Dam; Clearwater National Forest
    - Clinton, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Coeur d'Alene Basin, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Bunker Hill Superfund; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
    - Craig, Larry, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Crapo, Mike, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Crime, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Omnibus Crime Control Act
    - Defense, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Military; Homosexuality; Defense Department
    - Deficit, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Democratic Party, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Demographics, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Campaign, 1994; Idaho--Population
    - Echohawk, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Economy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      United States--Economy; Idaho--Economy; Budget Deficits
    - Education, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Employment, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      Idaho--Employment
    - Endangered Species, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Energy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      Energy--Taxation; Fall River Hydroelectric Project
    - Environment, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      Ecology; Environmental Protection Agency
    - Family, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Family and Medical Leave Act
    - Federal Election Committee, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Fletcher (Box 9, Folder 45)
      Fletcher, Penny
    - Foreign Affairs, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      International Relations; Haiti
    - Forest Health, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Franking, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Gambling, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Indians of North America--Gaming
    - Gem County, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Gary Glenn, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - GOP, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Republican Party
    - GOP - 1st District, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Race, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Campaign, 1994ty
      Echohawk, Larry; Batt, Phil
    - Guns, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Gun Control; Hunting; National Rifle Association
    - Health, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Rural Health Care; Medical Care; Health Care Reform
    - Hells Canyon, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Hispanics, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Hispanic Americans
    - House Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Idaho City, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Idaho City, Idaho
    - Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Idaho National Guard, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Indian Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Indians of North America--Idaho
    - Interior Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Israel, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Kempthorne, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Kootenai County, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Labor, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Land and Water Conservation Fund, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Land Use; Water Resources
    - Landfills, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Solid Waste
    - LaRocco, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Financial Disclosure
    - Larry LaRocco, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Larry LaRocco, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Latah, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Latah County
    - Letters to the Editor, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Constituents; Campaign, 1994
    - Letters to the Editor, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Letters to the Editor ), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Lewis County, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Lewiston, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Lewiston, Idaho
    - McMurray, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Campaign, 1994; Republican Party
      McMurray, Don
    - Meridian, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Meridian, Idaho
    - Mining, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Mining, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Mountain Home Air Force Base, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - National Biological Survey, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      Public Lands; Endangered Species Act
    - National Forests, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - National Services, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      National and Community Service Act; AmeriCorps
    - Nez Perce County, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Nuclear Waste, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - One Percent, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Idaho--Taxation; One percent Initiative
    - Originals, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Owyhee County, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Pacific Fish, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      Pacific Ocean--Fishing
    - Payette County, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Payette River, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      h.R.233
    - Payment in Lieu of Taxes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      Public Lands; Taxation
    - Piper Jaffray and Hopwood (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Legal Affairs; Sexual Harassment; Campaign, 1994
    - Private Property, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Railroads, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Re-inventing Government, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Government Spending; Bureaucracy
    - Rent to Own (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Rental Purchase Reform Act
    - River, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Idaho--Rivers; Boise River
    - Salmon, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Savings, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Savings Accounts
    - Seniors, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Shoshone County, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Coeur d'Alene Basin; Superfund; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
    - Silver Medal Bill, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Silver Medal Act
    - Spending, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Spending, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Staff, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Stallings, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Tait, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Idaho--Judiciary
      Tait, John
    - Taxes, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Telemedicine, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Telecommunications; Rural Health Care
    - Term Limits, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Timber, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Trade, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      GATT; NAFTA; International Economics
    - Tourism, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Town Meetings, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Training Range, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Training Range, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - United We Stand, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Balanced Budget Amendment
    - Valley County, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Payette River--Environmental Aspects; Cascade Reservoir
    - Valley County, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Cascade Reservoir
    - Veterans, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Votes, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - War on the West, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Public Lands; Mines and Mining
    - Washington County, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Water, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Weaver Case, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      Federal Bureau of Investigation; Ruby Ridge, Idaho
      Weaver, Randy